http://www.jeopardy.com/canadianprivacyaddendum

Search
HomeLatest J!BuzzNews & EventsBehind the ScenesContestantsMark Your CalendarContestant ZoneThis Week on Jeopardy!Tournament of Champions TrackerChampions ArchiveHall of FamePast TournamentsBe on J!Jeopardy! Anytime TestPrep CenterTake the Practice TestContestant FAQsThe J!EffectJ!Effect HomeSubmit Fan StoryJ!Alumni StoriesSubmit J!Alumni StoryGames & MoreJ!6J!6 AlexaJ!6 Google AssistantJEOPARDY! APPSInfinite Final J!New York TimesGet More J!J! StoreWatchFind Your StationStreamingAboutAlexClue CrewProduction TeamAwardsMedia CenterJ! FAQsGet Tickets
Canadian Addendum
If you are a resident of Canada, the following additions, alterations and modifications apply to our processing of your personal information in lieu of the relevant sections of the Privacy Policy. In the event of a conflict between the provisions of the Privacy Policy and the provisions of this Addendum, the provisions of this Addendum shall govern and control.
1. Collection of Information
Section 1(A)(i) of the Privacy Policy is deleted and replaced as follows:
Information SPE, its Service Providers and/or Third-Party Services may collect may include: personally identifiable information, which is information that identifies you personally, such as your first and last name, e-mail address, phone number, address, full payment account number, gender, age, interests, and recent and upcoming purchases ("Personal Information"). Personal Information, including, without limitation, SPE-Collected PI (defined below), once "de-identified" (i.e., the removal of personal identifiers from data to make it no longer personally identifiable) is non-Personal Information ("non-Personal Information") and may be used and shared without obligation to you, except as prohibited by applicable law. To the extent any non-Personal Information is combined by or on behalf of SPE with Personal Information SPE itself collects directly from you on the Service ("SPE-Collected PI"), SPE will treat the combined data as SPE-Collected PI under this Privacy Policy
If you use a "share with a friend" or similar feature on our website, we may collect your name and email address, as well as the name and email address of the recipient. We do not use the names or email addresses submitted in these circumstances for any other purpose without the consent of you or the email recipient to do so. Please ensure that you only submit email addresses of individuals with whom you have a personal or family relationship and who would want to receive the message from you.
2. Disclosure of Information
We and the third parties we employ to perform functions on our behalf may disclose your Personal Information (i) if we are required or permitted to do so by applicable US, Canadian or other law or legal process, and (ii) to Canadian, US or other foreign law enforcement authorities, courts and other government officials based on a lawful disclosure request.
3. Information Collected Automatically
(a) Cookies
In addition to the notice provided in section 1(B) of the Privacy Policy regarding the use of cookies, the following are additional examples of the way we use session and tracking cookies on the pages on our Service where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable. If you have registered with our Service, these cookies (1) may let us know who you are, (2) may be necessary to access your account information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver products and personalized services, and (3) may provide us and our service providers with information that we will use to personalize our Service in accordance with your preferences.
(b) Web Beacons
In addition to the notice provided in section 1(B) of the Privacy Policy regarding the use of web beacons, the following are additional examples of the way we use web beacons on our website: (i) to assist us in understanding which pages you have visited on our Service; and (ii) to help us optimize and tailor our websites for you and other future visitors to our Service.
4. Analytics and Advertising Tracking Technologies
In addition to the notice in section 11(B) of the Privacy Policy, some of the advertisers and Service Providers that perform advertising-related services for us and our partners may participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada’s ( "DAAC") Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. To learn more about how you can exercise certain choices regarding Interest-based Advertising, visit http://www.youradchoices.ca. Some of these companies may also be members of the Network Advertising Initiative ( "NAI"). To learn more about the NAI and your opt-out options for their members, see http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.
5. Accessing and Changing Information
To access, update or correct inaccuracies in your personal information or if you have a question or complaint about the manner in which we or our service providers treat your Personal Information, please contact our Privacy Officer [Jason_Spaltro@spe.sony.com] as set out under "Contact SPE" in the Privacy Policy.
©2020 Jeopardy Productions, Inc. "JEOPARDY!" and "America's Favorite Quiz Show" are registered trademarks of Jeopardy Productions, Inc. All rights reserved.
Sony Properties
Visit SonyPictures.com
Movies
Television
Games & Apps
Footer menu
Site Map
Terms & Conditions
©2020 Sony Pictures Entertainment Inc.
Facebook
Twitter
Instagram
YouTube
